Hello friends, Namaste, I am Ranveer Singh and a very warm welcome to
all of you once again to our channel.
Friends, if you are also a
Common Service Center operator, that is, a
driver from a CSC center, then friends, this
video is going to be special for you
because friends, today we are going to talk on this topic
that how you will be able to get two
wheeler third party
insurance from ICICI Columbus from your CSC center.
Friends, in this video we will
tell you live how you will be
able to get third party insurance from ICICI Columbus. So friends, if you are visiting the
channel for the first time, then subscribe to the channel
and
give a lovely like to the video because friends,
we keep getting similar latest videos
for you from time to time. So
friends, let's start the video. So
friends, first of all you have to log in to the Digital Seva
Portal. The
interface will open in this way, as
you all must be knowing how
people do it. After that, friends,
here you will get an icon which is of
insurance, so you have to click on it.
As friends, if you click, then the
next page will open in front of you like this.
Now here friends, you will get this  The
interface will open in this way, so here
you have to go to the last at the bottom, here
you will get an option of motor third
party, here friends
you have to click on motor third party, as if
friends, if you click here then
a next interface will open like this,
now here friends
you will find many companies, all those which are already connected with SSC, all those which are
connected with Common Service Center, they should come here,
you will find all the insurance companies here,
so friends, from which company do you
want to do insurance, friends, here
you will get all the companies,
for that friends, I will do it
from ICICI column here, so here
friends, you have to enter ICICI here, that is,
you have to write
ICICI in the search bar and after writing it
you will
see two options here, if you
click then the next page will
open in front of you like this, the one
which is loading here will
open like this, now friends, from here you have to
watch the video carefully and understand well
how to do the insurance,
for that here friends you get an option
of two wheeler here  Here friends,
you have to do two wheeler i.e. first quality
and here you get an option of two
wheeler TP third party, so we will
click on this, after that here
friends, you have to take a look at renewal, so
here friends, we do not have to do renewal and new,
here we have to do
renewal, so here we will
click on the renewal option and
click on continue here, after that the
next page which will come in front of us will be
direct like this and will
open here like this, now here
friends, what you have to do, the
dashboard has opened here, here you have to
fill all the details, whatever is the detail in the RC, the
registration number, you will fill it up here, that is, after seeing the registration number in the RC, you will
fill up the registration number here, like
friends, you will fill up the registration number, after that friends, you will
fill up the registration number,
after that friends, here you get an option,
you get the option of get RTO details, here you
get the option of get RTO details, in this way
you must be seeing, you have to click on this option,
as if you
will click on this option, then the details which are in front of you
Everything will be filled, the date when your
vehicle will be registered will be shown and friends, the
RTO you belong to will be shown and all the
status will be shown here, in this way,
if it does not come here then friends you
can also fill it separately, if it does
not come in filling then you can also fill it separately,
everything has been filled here automatically,
so you will see everything here, whatever is
your vehicle model, whatever it is, everything will be
filled here automatically,
after that you do not have to do anything here,
if you want cover then you can do it,
but if you do not want to do anything here, you have to
click here,
after that the next page will open like this,
here friends you will see the premium, whatever amount
you have to pay here,
it will be shown here,
like here friends it is 784,
after that you will click here again,
now you have to fill further details,
as friends some details
are already filled here, like
friends your engine number is done, your chassis
number is done, whatever is there, the details are already filled here  It is
already fat, friends, if there is
no fat then you can put it here,
after that here friends, if you
want the description of the bank, then you can fill it up here, you
can leave it, after that
friends, here in the details of add nominee,
you have to add a nominee here, so you
will click on the nominee option here, if you want to add other details here, then you
can do it, brother, you can leave it, then
here you will click on the add nominee
option, then an
option to add a nominee will open in front of you,
here friends, you have to
fill up the nominee name, whatever is the name of the nominee, you have to
fill it up there, after that
friends, here you have to
fill up the age of the nominee relationship nominee,
you
can also fill it up as per the Aadhar card, after that create new
customer, that is, friends, now here you have to
fill in the customer's address i.e. name etc. here, so simply,
whatever you have to select here,
after that in the name options here  The
name of the customer which you have to fill up here
and after that, after filling up here,
you will
see an option of date of birth here, friends,
here you have to select the date of birth
from this calendar, whatever is the
customer's data birth, you have to
select it here according to the Aadhar card,
after that friends, here you have to
fill the address in the correspondent address line van, you
can enter the landmark in the landmark,
you will enter the pin code in the pin code, whatever is the
area code post code, select here
in the city, which friends, you have to select in intercity,
whatever it is,
after that you have to select whatever
is the state of the customer, you will select it here and here friends,
you have to fill up the email ID
and
fill up the mobile number here and here friends,
you have to fill up the PAN card number, if yes, then you can
fill it,
after that friends, here you have to
click on generate propose, as friends, if
you click on this, then the next page will appear in
front of you like this  It will open, now
friends, you get the proposal number here,
that is, friends, in a way, you get the
proposal number here,
now friends, you do
not have to do anything here, you have to click on the buy nine
option here, like friends, if
you click on the buy nine option, then
friends, it will take you to the CSC one, it will
retire you because there you will
not be deducted any fee, so friends, we have reached our CC
wallet, here friends, you have to
enter the password, whatever your password
is, you have to enter your password here, so
friends, we
fill in our password here, you can also enter your
password in this way,
after filling up the password, friends, you have to
click here, after that, here friends,
you have to fill in the wallet PIN number here,
whatever your number is,
you have to fill it here, after that, you will
click on this option here, like
friends, if you click on the option, then the
payment will be done,
after that, here friends, your policy will be
completed, the fee will also be paid,
after that, here friends, you get the policy number
and the policy start date here  The
policy end date is available here,
friends, you can see it here,
after that, friends, you have to
click on download policy here,
like friends, if you
click on the download policy option here, then
your policy will be downloaded,
you have to double click here and open the policy and
check it once, in
this way your policy will be downloaded here,
friends, you can print it out
and give it to the customer, your
policy is ready, friends, in this
way you will be
able to easily make a policy from your CSC portal, whether you want to do it for
third party or first party
or for motorcycle or for car, whatever you want to do,
friends,
you can do it very easily, friends, if you have any
kind of doubt or question, then you
can comment below, friends, if
you liked this information, then
you must like it, we will meet again
in the next video of this type, till then
Jai Hind Jai